原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译     累
校对     累
时间轴     西·查
后期     累
总监     累
牛仔竞技赛的条条大路都通向这里
Every road from the rodeo leads right here.
今天什么日子
What day is it?
今天是医院的发薪日
Well, it's payday, for the hospital.
他们和你一起中了彩票
They won the lottery with you...
我拿笔记下来了
Had to write all this shit down...
你的颈部有压迫性骨折
You have a compression fracture in your neck
背后还有两处
and two in your back.
一块骨头碎片压在你的脊椎上
A bone fragment's pressed against your spine,
还不知道该怎么弄出来
can't figure out how to get that out.
你的髋关节粉碎性骨折  他们刚给你换了新的
Shattered your hip, which they just up and replaced.
医生说你是他见过的最年轻的
Doctor said you're the youngest person he's ever done that to.
所以恭喜你
So, congratulations for that.
他想让你今天起来走走
He wants you up and walking today.
我觉得根本没戏
How that's possible I have... I have no idea...
你有三级脑震荡
You have a grade three concussion.
如果你感到恶心或懵圈
We're supposed to bring you back to the hospital
我们就得把你送回医院
if you experience nausea or confusion.
我问了还有没有其他症状
I asked if there's other symptoms
因为恶心和懵圈是你的正常状态
since nauseous and confused is your natural state of being.
他们说你的瞳孔可能会放大
They said your eyes might dilate.
我们会留意的
So, we'll be on the lookout for that.
我胳膊怎么了
What's wrong with my arm?
他们没提你的胳膊
Well, they didn't mention your arm.
所以肯定没事
So it must be fine.
感觉好像有事啊
Doesn't look fine.
跟其他的比起来  不算什么了
Well, compared to the rest of this shit, it's fine.
我要怎么
How am I gonna...
我怎么付得起呢
How am I gonna pay for all this?
医院也很好奇
Well, the hospital's pretty curious about that themselves.
看着我
Look at me.
医院账单不用你担心
Hospital bill's not a concern.
但你得向我保证
But you gotta make me a promise.
别再参加牛仔竞技了
No more rodeo.
这是唯一一件
It's the only thing that ever...
让我觉得自己有价值的事情
ever made me feel like I was worth something.
嗯
Yeah.
我猜也是
Well, I figured as much.
学套索吧
Learn to rope.
最惨也只是失去一根拇指
All you're risking is a thumb, and...
反正你有两个
you got two of those.
达顿先生
Mister Dutton, uh...
谢谢
Thank you.
学套索吧  吉米
Yeah, well, learn to rope, Jimmy.
我可不会帮你付两次医疗费
I'm not paying for this shit twice.
吉米
Okay, Jimmy.
我们扶你起来  让你走走
We're going to help you up so you can walk.
我不太想走路  所以
Don't really feel like walking, so...
你的髋关节换过了  所以你得活动一下
Your hip replacement needs you to move around a bit.
但我们得先移除你的导尿管
But first we need to remove your catheter.
好  抬起来
All right, just lift.
好了
There we go.
好  深呼吸
All right, deep breath.
拉的时候你会感觉到一点压力
You're going to feel a little pressure when I pull, okay?
你活下来了
You survived.
好吧  最大的谜题先被我解开了
All right, getting the mystery out of the way right up front, huh?
它是肿了吗
Is it just... is it swollen from the...
本来就是这样
I think it's the way God made that one.
真是醉了
This isn't happening.
我可以帮忙吗
Can I help?
你是亲属吗
Are you a relative?
是的  我  我是他女朋友
Yeah, I'm, uh... I'm his girlfriend.
没问题  过来  抓住一只胳膊
Yeah, sure. Just, uh, come over here. Grab an arm.
来
All right, here.
我不知道我适不适合
I don't know if I can be in a relationship
和一个如此缺乏判断力的人恋爱
with someone who shows such poor judgment.
我是绕桶赛手
Well, I'm a barrel racer.
肯定缺乏判断力啊
So bad judgment's just part of the package.
你没养狗吧
Don't have a dog, do you?
其实我养了两条
I have two, actually.
怪不得
That fuckin' figures.
黄石
第三季  第四集
漆马赌场酒店
这样不合适吧  主席
I am not sure this is appropriate, Chairman.
我不是詹金斯财产的律师
I don't represent the Jenkins' estate.
我是说剩下的财产
Or, whatever's left of it, I mean.
我现在不关心他的财产
His estate is not my concern at the moment.
这个合法吗
Is there any validity to this?
停止命
他们在下象棋
It's a chess move.
这样会让你处于防守状态  阻止你建房
It puts you on the defensive. Stops you from building.
但他们赢不了啊
But... But they don't have a winnable case.
赢的定义是什么
Well, define winnable.
如果你是指对他们有利的判决  那是没有
If you mean a judgment in their favor? No.
但是他们可以拖上好几年
But, you know, they can drag this out for years.
这不是一个举债经营的土地开发商
This isn't a leveraged land developer,
这是一个价值数十亿美元的公司
this is a multibillion dollar corporation
他们可以花五千万到一亿美元的律师费
that can spend 50, 100 million dollars in legal fees.
而且现实是
And the reality is, that,
我觉得他们根本不想要你的土地
you know, I doubt they even want your land.
他们只是不想让印第安赌场
They just don't want an Indian casino
位于他们规划的社区附近
adjacent to a planned community.
所以他们想买下我的产权
So, they'll try to buy me out.
我觉得他们不会费那个劲
I doubt they'll even bother.
我能问你个问题吗  私人问题
May I ask you a question? A personal question?
你当初为什么要建赌场
Why build a casino in the first place?
真正的原因是什么
I mean what's the real reason?
交通更加便捷的好地方还有很多
There are better locations with far better access.
这个山谷有两个未来
There's two futures with this valley,
一个是土地被二套房和爱好农场剥夺
one with the land stripped of the second homes
然后回到从前的样子
and hobby farms, and returned to the ways it used to be...
你开了20英里到公园
You drive twenty miles into the park
整个国家曾经都觉得很正常
and that's how our whole nation looked at one time.
现代社会希望人们去上学
Modern society wants people to go to school
学着做生意赚钱
and learn a trade to make money
买吃的  穿的  居住的地方
to buy food, clothes, a place to live.
但在没有被人类蹂躏过的土地上
But on land that hasn't been ravaged by man,
不需要买吃的
you don't need to buy food.
而是寻找吃的
You just go find it.
不用买衣服  而是制作衣服
You don't buy clothes, you make them.
不用盖房子  而是寻找遮盖物
And you don't build houses, you seek shelter.
和土地一起生活  而非在土地上生活
You live with the land. Not on it.
你说有两个未来  另一个是什么
You said two futures. What's the other?
另一个是你居住的地方
The other's where you live.
混凝土世界里的木屋
Concrete worlds with stick houses
没有肥料和洒水器就无法生存的草
and grass that can't survive without fertilizer and sprinklers.
总有一天  这个星球会把你们
Some day this planet's going to shake your world
像雨水一样甩掉
off its back like rainwater.
赌场给了我足够的钱来确保这件事一定会发生
The casino gives me the money I need to make sure that happens.
第一个未来是唯一的未来
The first future is the only future.
恐怕人们更喜欢混凝土
People prefer concrete, I'm afraid.
没人喜欢你的未来
Nobody wants your future.
你的世界根本就没有人
No one in your world.
好吧
Well...
我很想告诉你该怎么对抗他们
I wish I could tell you how to fight them.
如果有人知道如何对抗他们
If anyone knew how to fight them,
就不会有什么保留地了
there'd be no such thing as reservations.
你怎么看  老莫
What do you think, Mo?
我觉得你需要的是律师  不是他
I think you need a lawyer and not him.
像他这样的人自有用处
Well, men like him have their use.
但是这件事他帮不上忙
But no, not for this...
我们一直都知道如何对抗他们  汤姆
We've always known how to fight them, Tom.
我们没有行动  只是因为我们不想变得像他们一样
We just didn't 'cause we didn't want to be like them.
我觉得你该变得像他们一样了
I think it's time you be like them.
人民永远不会原谅我的
The people would never forgive me.
-这是为了人民  -他们还是不会原谅我
- It's for the people.  -Still won't forgive me.
但我还是得行动
But I'm going to do it anyway.
帮我接通约翰·达顿的电话
Get John Dutton on the phone for me.
安吉拉·布鲁·桑德  谢谢
Angela Blue Thunder, please.
雷恩沃特主席
Chairman Rainwater.
你跟她谈过以后必须要烧鼠尾草
You're going to need to sage off after you speak with her.
我知道
I know.
舒瓦茨和梅耶
你戳了一只大熊啊  贝丝
That's a pretty big bear to poke, Beth.
他们在山谷的活动让我们的股份增长了20%
And their activity in the valley has our holdings up twenty percent.
我没有戳他们  这是个机会  鲍勃
I'm not poking them, It's an opportunity, Bob.
如果他们认为机场审批没问题
If they thought their airport approvals were guaranteed,
他们肯定会在屋顶上尖叫的
they would be screaming it from the rooftops.
现在还不到卖空的时候吧
Tell me it is not ripe to short.
你放话出去  他们就会知道是你了
When you put the word out, they're going to know it's you.
我不会放话出去的
Well, I'm not gonna put the word out.
你来
You are.
可以卖空了  你不同意吗
It is ripe to short. Do you disagree?
他们暴露了  没错
They're exposed, it's true.
这会让他们伤得很深
And it's gonna cut them pretty deep,
然后他们会全力反击的
and they are going to come out swinging.
这就是塞伦盖蒂的生活吧
Yeah, well, that's just life in the Serengeti, I guess.
你想打给基金经理还是媒体
You want to call the fund managers or the press?
我打给经理
I'll take the managers.
但是只能稍微漏点水  贝丝
But, Beth, just a little leak.
稍微漏点水  不要炸掉水坝
Just a leak, you know? Do not blow up the dam.
拜托  鲍勃  你还不了解我嘛
Oh, come on, Bob. You know me better than that.
所以我才这么说的
That's why I'm saying just a leak.
中等程度的漏水
A medium leak.
既然做了  就要做的漂亮
Anything worth doing is worth doing right.
对吗
Right?
谢谢  回见
Thank you. I'll call you back.
-股票交易员  -亚当·提利还在主持新闻发布会吗
- Stock trader. - Hi, is Adam Tilly still running press releases?
-是的  -帮我接通一下
- Yep. - Put me through to him.
稍等
One moment.
那面旗是干什么的
What's that flag for?
用来教这些小马驹如何正确操控自己的身体
Well, it teaches these colts to use their bodies
然后再用真正的牛
the right way before I put them on a cow.
为什么不直接用牛呢
Why not just use a cow?
我靠  女士  那不就相当于在拳赛中
For hell's sakes, lady, that's kind of like practicing a fist fight
以赛代练了么
when you're already in the middle of one,
明白我的意思吗
ya know what I mean?
这是个艰难的决定
A tough call.
操  你是州长
Oh fuck, you're the Governor.
女士  对不起  操  我
Miss, I'm sorry. Fuck, I...
-我很抱歉  -闭嘴  杰克
- I'm sorry. - Shut up, Jake.
我找约翰
I'm looking for John.
他在山上的夏季营地
He's up there at the summer camp.
你能指条路吗
Well, can you point the way?
那边
It's that way but
但你们开车上不去啊
you ain't gonna get them machines up there.
你会骑马吗
Can you, uh, can you ride a horse?
我会
Yeah, I can ride.
太好了  我去给你备一匹马
Perfect, I'll go saddle you one.
女士  我们不能让你骑马
Ma'am, we can't have you on a horse.
-出于安全考虑  -他
- Safety concerns. - He's, uh...
他说不能骑马  所以
He's saying no to the horse, so...
他担心我摔下去蒙大拿就完了
He's worried Montana won't survive if I fall off.
那好吧
Well, hell, uh...
我有个更好的主意
I got a better idea.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - Yes, Ma'am.
原来你一直躲在这里啊
So, this is where you've been hiding out, huh?
这地方不错吧
Yeah, well, pretty good spot, huh?
是啊  我明白你为什么这么努力维护这里了
Yeah, I can see why you fight so hard for it.
是啊  没人
Yeah. No one, uh...
这里没有人会质疑
No one questions it from here.
什么风把你吹来了
To what do I owe the pleasure?
什么风  约翰
The pleasure, John?
我觉得你在树林里待太久了
I think you've been in the woods too long.
凯斯呢
Where's Kayce?
嗯
Yeah.
杰克
Jake...
你回屋子去找杰米
I need you to run back to the house and grab Jamie.
那得花点时间
That's... That's gonna take me a little while.
嗯  别提前回来
Yeah. Make sure of it.
遵命
Yes, sir.
约翰说他任命你当牲畜委员会委员
John says you refused his appointment
可你拒绝了
to Livestock Commissioner.
我不是政客
Yeah, I'm not a politician.
那不是政客的工作
That's not a job for a politician.
你父亲确实是出于这个目的  但是
I mean, sure, your father used it that way, but...
那是因为他有能力
That's because he could.
蒙大拿的牧民需要的
What the cattlemen of Montana need
是保护他们生计的人
is someone to protect their livelihood.
这就是工作的本质
That's the job.
你可以做得很好
And at that, you would excel.
现在那是杰米的工作了
Well, that's Jamie's job now.
不  我需要杰米做别的事
No, I need Jamie for something else.
你父亲也一样
So does your father.
要他干什么
Need him for what?
帮我阻止这个山谷变成城市
To help me prevent this valley from becoming a city.
变成城市又如何
What do you care if it becomes a city?
变成城市对你更有利吧
Feel like a city would be good for you.
这就是我的立场最大的冲突
That's the great conflict of my position, you know?
如何让蒙大拿继续发展
How to keep Montana growing
但是不失去蒙大拿的特色
without losing that thing that makes it Montana.
那就拒绝呗
Well, then just say no.
就不会有城市了
There'll be no city.
如果我拒绝了  他们就会去找同意的人
If I say no, they just go and get someone that says yes,
到时候我的工作就被那个人抢了
and that person has my job.
我不懂
Don't make sense.
嗯  是挺难懂的
No, it doesn't make sense to you.
但是杰米懂了
But it makes sense to Jamie.
他知道怎么利用法律来拒绝
He knows how to make the law say no.
我要任命他为检察长
I'm appointing him Attorney General,
然后任命你为牲畜委员会委员
and I'm appointing you Livestock Commissioner,
你要抛开害怕变成你父亲那样的恐惧
and you will set aside your fears of becoming like your father
承担起这个责任
and take on this responsibility
因为如果你不愿意  这一切都会消失
because all of this disappears if you don't.
命运很难逃避  不是吗
Destiny's a hard thing to run from, isn't it?
但是比我想象中快多了
Just turned out to be a lot faster than I thought.
那就这么定了
Well, that's settled then.
如果我答应你
If I do this,
我得按我的方式来
I gotta do it my way.
这是你的办公室
It's your office.
随你啊
You can do it however you want.
亲爱的
Hello, dear.
今天过的怎么样
How was your day?
当你爸爸厌倦了睡在外面
When your dad gets tired of sleeping outside,
他就想知道他女儿睡在哪里了
he's gonna wonder where his daughter's sleeping.
幸运的是
Yeah, well, lucky for us,
他最喜欢在外面睡觉了
sleeping outside is his favorite thing to do.
我们得小心点  不然我会养成习惯的  亲爱的
We gotta be careful or I'm gonna get used to shit, darling.
我就是这么计划的
Well, that's the plan.
你还有计划了
Oh, you got plans, do you?
我对一切都有计划
I have a plan for everything.
一个人坐在自己的网里
Just sitting in your web, all alone,
制定计划
Coming up with plans.
-你还挺幽默  -可不嘛
- And a sense of humor? - Yeah, you know.
天啊  之前怎么没发现呢
God, where did that come from?
开玩笑  我一直都很幽默
What are you talking about? I've been funny all my life.
你有很多特质  但并不包括幽默  宝贝
You are many things, but baby, funny is not one of them.
抱歉
Sorry.
再叫我一声
Call me that again.
叫你什么
Call you what?
宝贝  再叫一声
Baby. Say that again.
你喜欢吗
You like that, do you?
是的
Yeah, I do.
好的  宝贝
Okay, baby.
我该怎么叫你
What should I call you?
妻子
Wife.
我不是那个意思
I didn't mean that.
我给你做一顿晚餐吧
I'm gonna make you dinner for once.
我的车呢
Where's my ride?
他会回来的
He'll be back.
什么时候
When?
那就
Well, that's...
...that's...
很难说了  喝一杯吗
...that's hard to say. Want a drink?
这和绑架差不多了
This is... This is almost kidnapping.
放松  莉奈儿  好好享受日落吧
Oh, just relax, Lynelle. Enjoy the sunset.
好吧  只要你别用那种表情看我
Fine, as long as you don't give me that look.
什么表情
What look?
这个表情
That look.
"脱掉裙子  进我帐篷"的表情
That "drop your dress and get in my outfitter tent" look.
我哪有
I'm not giving you any look.
因为我不会留下的  所以你还是少来吧
Yeah, because I'm not staying, so you can just stop it.
别闹
Stop it.
我没闹啊
I'm not doing anything.
靠  约翰
Goddammit, John.
为什么不论何时何地
How is it that you're always three steps ahead
你都领先所有人三步呢
of everybody everywhere you go?
我只是经常坐下来思考
It's just a lot of sitting and thinking...
坐下来思考
thinking and sitting.
你又来了
And you're doing it again.
哪有
I'm not doing anything.
我明天一早就得走
I have to leave first thing in the morning.
你想在这过夜吗
You wanna spend the night?
你真混
You're such a bastard.
明天一早啊
First thing in the morning, I meant.
二早怎么样
How about second?
你上次看日落是什么时候  州长
When's the last time you watched a sunset, Governor?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我明白他们为什么想卖掉这个梦想了
I can see why this is the dream they want to sell.
是的  但你不能卖  你得自己争取
Yep... but you can't sell this. You gotta earn it.
你得体会  这是他们永远无法理解的
You gotta live it. And that's what they'll never understand.
但他们只想卖
But they only want to sell it.
他们不在乎梦想是否成真
And they could care less about the dream coming true.
这就是你要理解的
That's what you've got to understand.
你还在
You still here?
有难同当嘛
Through thick and thin.
风雨同舟嘛
How you feel?
屁股疼
Hip hurts.
肋骨疼  背疼
Ribs hurt. Back hurts.
你的鸡鸡怎么样了
How's your pecker?
鸡鸡
Pecker.
应该还行
Seems fine.
很好
Good.
我在想我们应该完成这笔买卖
I was thinking we should consummate this deal.
听起来不错  但是
That sounds great, but...
我不知道他们有没有告诉你  我的背断了
I don't know if they told you, my back is broken.
你是说不行吗
Are you saying no?
不  不  不是
No. No. No, no, no.
我只是
I just, um...
我不想瘫痪
I don't want it to paralyze me.
可能会让你瘫痪一两分钟
Well, it might paralyze you for a minute or two.
你不是处男吧
You're not a virgin, are you?
什么
What?
拜托  别这样
Come on, no. Come on.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
因为你刚才的表情很像害怕的处男
'Cause you got like a scared virgin face.
不  我不是处男  你是处女吗
No, I'm not a virgin. Are you a virgin?
我是绕桶赛手
I'm a barrel racer.
失去处女身就像是
Losing your virginity is like,
参赛的必要条件
it's like a requirement to compete.
我们还是慢慢来吧
Maybe we should, uh, just slow down on this whole deal.
你就是处男
You are!
我不是处男
I am not a virgin.
是因为我吗  你不喜欢我吗
Is it me? Are you not attracted to me?
你不喜欢也没关系  但你得告诉我
Cause it's okay if you're not, but you've got to tell me.
不
No, it's...
我是说  你
I mean, you're...
你太漂亮了
You're too pretty.
我这样的人配不上你
You're too pretty for a guy like me.
她叫什么名字
What's her name?
-谁  -你的初夜  她叫什么名字
- Who? - Your first. What was her name?
我没有  我不记得了
I didn't... I can't even remember.
严格来说我还没做过爱  好吗
Okay, no, I haven't technically had sex, all right?
你开心了吗
Are you happy?
我觉得我的大脚趾里还残留着一点男子气概
I think there's still a shred of manhood left in my big toe
你出去的时候也可以践踏一下
if you want to step on that on the way out.
你干什么  你在干什么
What are you... what are you doing?
我要破你的处
I'm being your first.
别紧张
Don't be nervous.
很爽的
It's supposed to be fun.
我害怕当你的视力恢复时
I'm scared that when your eyesight returns
只要看我一眼
you're gonna take one look at me--
我的视力没问题
I see just fine.
你才是瞎子呢  吉米
You're the one who's blind, Jimmy.
但我也会帮你治好的
But I'm going to fix that too...
早啊
Morning.
的确很早
Yeah, sure is.
宝贝  回来躺下
Baby? Come back to bed.
我
I'll be, uh...
早餐几点
What time's breakfast?
约翰
John?
应该是过一会吧
A little later this morning.
明白
Understood.
回头见
I'll see you in...
嗯  好的
Yeah. You know.
不吃早餐吗
No breakfast?
不了  我
Nah, I got a...
我得去参加比尤特的小母牛拍卖会
heifer auction in Butte I gotta go to.
我搞砸了  不是吗
I fucked it up, didn't I?
我把一切都搞砸了  我不是故意的
I fucked the whole thing... I didn't mean it.
听着
Hey, listen.
我之所以不跟你聊明天的事  贝丝
The only reason why I don't bring up tomorrow with you, Beth,
是因为每次我一聊
is because every fucking time I do,
你就逃走了
you run away.
我把和你在一起的每一天都当做礼物
I look at every day with you as a gift.
我的明天
My tomorrows are...
都属于你
Well, they're all yours.
来
Here.
我不知道还能叫你什么
There is no word that I'd rather call you.
如果你希望我这么叫你  那我没问题
I mean, if that's what you want.
你知道我为什么总是逃跑吗
You know why I always run away?
我只能给你这么多  里普
There's only so much I can give to you, Rip.
不
No.
你可以给我一切
You can give me everything.
不
No.
我不能生孩子
I can't have children.
你要知道这一点
You need to know that.
和我在一起是一条死路
Being with me is the end of you.
我一出生就在一条死路上  亲爱的
I was born on a dead end road, honey.
这个世界不需要我的后代
This world doesn't need another generation of me.
那可不一定
I wouldn't be so sure.
我不喜欢让一群孩子
I don't want a bunch of kids
在这个房子里跑来跑去
running around this fucking house.
我连狗都不喜欢
I mean, I don't even like dogs.
我只需要你
You're all I need.
你想让我叫你什么都可以
I'll call you whatever you want.
暂时叫贝丝吧
Beth is fine. For now.
那就叫你贝丝  亲爱的
Beth it is, darling. Beth it is.
你得去上班了
You gotta go to work.
好的
Okay.
不得不说
I gotta say,
我喜欢看你这样坐在门廊上
I like leaving you sitting here on the porch like this.
要是我回来的时候你还在
Be a whole lot better though,
那就更好了
if you were here when I got home.
那到时候看看吧
Well, I'll see what I can do about that.
股票持续下跌
And stocks continue their downward trend
又有两家石油公司被列入美国贸易黑名单
as two more oil companies were added to the U.S. Trade blacklist.
两家公司正在因证券欺诈被调查
Both companies are currently being investigated for securities fraud.
本日最大的一次下跌中
And in the largest dip of the day,
投资公司市场股票下跌了7.5%
investment firm Market Equities falls over 7.5%.
市场股票集团
-我操  -引起了整个行业的恐慌
- What the fuck? - ...causing industry-wide panic as analysts...
市场股票  蒙大拿投资失败吗
那个贱人
That fucking bitch.
市场股票集团  股票下滑
见我烧什么都没用  汤姆
There is no protection from me, Tom.
你知道的
You know that.
这才不到一年
It's barely been a year
你就在烧鼠尾草祈祷改变
and already you're burning sage praying for a change,
你自己怎么不改变呢
instead of being it.
我想让这里变得更美好
I'm trying to make it a better place.
到目前为止你所做的
All you've managed to do thus far
只是用我们所有的赌场利润
is take all of our casino profits
买了一家财富五百强公司
and buy land a Fortune 500 Company
要从你手中偷走的土地
is about to steal from you.
而且你对此无能为力
And there's nothing you can do about it.
所以我才找你过来
You're what I'm doing about it.
你知道人们是怎么说和魔鬼做交易的吗
You know what they say about making deals with the devil.
我不知道  安吉拉  人们怎么说
No, I don't, Angela. What do they say?
这是最大的谜团  汤姆
That's the big mystery, Tom.
你这是答应了吗
Is that a "yes"?
你会帮忙吗
You'll help?
你这么想也行吧
If that's what you want to call it.
她并不邪恶  老莫
She's not evil, Mo.
她只是很生气  她想惩罚这个世界
She's just angry and trying to punish the world
对她所做的一切
for everything it did to her.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
这就是邪恶的意思
That's what evil means.
-好凉  -泰特
- It's cold! - Tate!
你一周没洗澡了  你闻起来跟山羊一样
You haven't bathed in a week. You smell like a goat.
别跑
Just stay--
-给我回来  -来抓我呀
- Come back here. - Catch me.
他和你一样讨厌洗澡
Well, he's got your aversion to bathing.
我不讨厌洗澡
I don't mind bathing.
我只是不喜欢一个人洗
I just don't like doing it alone.
这不是一码事
That's not the same thing.
结果还是一样的  不是吗
The result's the same, though, ain't it?
结晶跑进了树林
The result just ran off into the woods.
我们要在这里待多久
How long are we staying here?
我不知道  宝贝
I don't know, baby.
我现在没心思去想以后的事
I'm having a hard time thinking past "right now."
不行的  我们不可能永远这样生活下去
This isn't real. We can't live like this forever.
永远压根就不存在  宝贝
There's no such thing as forever, baby.
我们能做的就是活在当下
All we can do is live like there's no tomorrow
因为世界总有一天会消失的
'cause one day we'll be right.
怎么了
What is it?
狼
Wolf.
-还是那只狼吗  -是的
- What, the same one? - Yeah.
我觉得它喜欢看我们
I think he likes watching us.
它不是在看  它是在研究我们
He's not watching, he's studying us.
研究什么
Studying what?
它想知道如果它追小牛跑时我们会有什么反应
Wants to know what we'll do when he goes after our calves.
我警告过你
I warned you.
你要去哪儿
Hey, where are you going?
回营地吧  宝贝  没事的
Just go back to camp, baby. It's okay.
你干嘛去
What are you going to do?
我去杀了它
I'm gonna kill him.
你敢
Don't you dare.
宝贝  他靠
Baby, he'll feed on every--
不要停止爱我  转去杀戮
Don't stop loving me to kill something.
过来
Just come here.
爱我就好
Just... Just love me.
你可以明天再杀它
You can kill him tomorrow.
下一批到了
And our next lot coming in.
六头安格斯后备母牛
Six replacement Angus heifers.
六头安格斯后备母牛起拍价五百
Let's start these six replacement Angus off 500 dollars?
有人出五百吗  五百块
Anybody give me 500 dollars. I need 500...
五百  有人出六百吗
I got 500, anybody go six?
这是我们喜欢的直背母牛
This is that straight-backed bunch we liked.
六百了  有人出七百吗  七百  七百
I got 600 anybody go 7 now, 7 now, 7 now
七百了  有人出八百吗  八百了
I got 7, anybody go 8? Oh! I got 8 right there.
有人出九百吗  八百了  有人出九百吗
Anybody go 9? I got 800, anybody go 9?
九百  九百了  有人出一千吗
Now 9, now 9, I got 9. Anybody go 1000?
九百了  有人出一千了
900 wup! I got 1000 dollars right there.
有人出一千一吗  一千了  有人出一千一吗
Anybody go 11. I have 1000, anybody gonna go 11 now
一千一  有人出一千一吗
11 now, I got 1000 anybody go 11?
有人出一千一吗
I have 1000 anybody go 1100 dollars?
一千一  有人出一千一吗
1100 dollars, I got anybody go to 11?
蒙大拿农场和饲料
一千块成交
I have a sale right there, 1000 dollars.
太好了
Hell, yeah.
-约翰肯定很高兴  -嗯
- John'll like that. - Sure.
-准备好了吗  走吧  -嗯
- You ready? Let's roll. - Yep.
走  快走
Go, go!
过来  鲍勃  过来
Come on, Bob. Come on, come on.
科尔比
Hey, Colby!
把夏洛来牛弄回去  那不是我们的
Turn that charolais back, it ain't ours.
回去  不行
Come on. No.
进去  回去  去去去
Get in, get it, hop, hop, hop! Hop, hop!
进去  去去去
Get in, get in, hop.
那个瘦女孩可以啊
That skinny girl's a hand,
是啊  真的可以
Yeah. I gotta say it.
她怎么样了
How's she working out?
你得定义一下"怎么样"
Well, you gotta define "working out."
小子们丢下她一个人吗
Boys leaving her alone?
丢下她一个人
Leaving her alone?
那个小土狼
That little hyena,
她看男人的眼神就像在看租来的骡子
she looks at a man like he's a rented mule.
她把工棚里的人吓的
She got the bunkhouse so scared
都快和鸡一起睡了
they're goin' to bed with the chickens.
把牛带去新的围栏  好吗
Bring 'em all to the new pen, will ya?
我们随后就到
We'll be right behind you.
你喝完了  对吧
You was done with that, wasn't you?
现在是喝完了
I am now.
你在后面还好吗  宝贝
How you doing back there, baby?
挺好  谢谢
Fine. Thanks.
好的
All right.
你应该坐在老娘的腿上
'Cause you ought be up here on mama's lap,
不过没关系  没关系
but that's all right. That's okay.
你们都觉得我是在开玩笑吧
Y'all think I'm joking.
很不幸  我们并不知道
No, unfortunately, we don't.
搞什么
What in the...
他们把围栏剪了
They cut the fucking fence.
现在打架也太早了
It's too early to get in a fight.
你们好啊
How you doing?
这些乡巴佬想干嘛
What do these rednecks want?
你们不能来这里
Listen, you can't be here.
这里是私人领地
This is private property.
这是国家公园啊
This is a national park.
那是国家公园
That's national park.
这是达顿农场
This is the Dutton Ranch.
牌子上写着"黄石"  上面有个很大的Y
Sign says "Yellowstone." Got a big fucking Y on it.
Y代表黄石农场
The Y is for the Yellowstone Ranch.
你不是说达顿农场么
You said Dutton Ranch.
这里是达顿黄石农场
It's the Yellowstone Dutton Ranch.
你们去马路对面吧
Listen, I need you to move across the road
不然我就以非法入侵罪传讯你们了
or I'm gonna have to cite you for trespassing.
这徽章上写着"牲畜委员会探员"
That badge says "livestock agent."
没错
That's right.
这他妈是放牛警察
It's the fucking cow police.
瞧瞧这个粉头发的乡巴佬  恶狠狠地盯着我
Look at this pink-haired hick mad-dogging me.
你有意见吗  婊子
You got a problem, bitch?
你他妈说啥
Fuck you just say to me?
叫你婊子
Called you a fucking bitch.
提特
Teeter!
我操
Ah fuck!
开什么玩笑
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
臭傻逼
Motherfucker!
你死定了
You're a fucking dead man.
你他妈
You're fucking--
我他妈打死你
I'll fucking shoot you!
那你就死定了
It'll be the last fucking thing you ever do.
那就动手啊
Better get after it, then.
太迟了
Too late.
哪个傻逼是你们老大
Which one of these assholes is the boss of you?
哪个傻逼
Which one of these motherfuckers?
那个大胡子
The big guy with the beard.
他吗
Him?
-他吗  -是的
- Him? - Yeah.
起来
Get up.
我再给你最后一次机会
I'm gonna give you one last chance.
现在不走  就别走了
You leave now or you never leave.
我直接把你就地埋了
I'll bury you where you fucking stand.
滚出去
Get the fuck out of here.
-听到了吧  -快点  滚出去
- You heard him. - Let's go. Get out of here.
快点
Let's go.
滚出去
Get the fuck out of here.
-后面交给你了  -没问题
- Why don't you cover my back? - Got you.
科尔比  你没事吧
Colby, you all right?
我的手好像断了
I think I broke my hand.
那没事  死不了
That's a far cry from your heart.
罗恩
Ron?
我们只是让他们离开这里
All we did was ask them to leave.
好了  走吧
All right, come on.
你呢  提特  你还好吗
What about you, Teeter? You okay?
有意思
That is fun.
-那群混蛋沿着观光路线要去斯特吉斯  -嗯
- Bunch of assholes taking the scenic route to Sturgis. - Yep.
他们回来拿摩托的时候
You know, when they come back for them bikes,
肯定会把这里弄得一团糟
they gonna fuck this field up something fierce.
也许吧
Probably so.
修围栏吧  走吧
Let's go fix the fence. Come on.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
这是你的地盘
This is your field.
你们要纵火吗
You gonna burn it?
这就是你们的计划吗
That's your plan?
你们可能也会被烧死的
Might burn you with it.
为什么
Why?
为什么要这么做
Why would you do that?
我们没有打扰任何人  我们只是想找点乐子
We weren't bothering anyone. We were just having some fun.
这个地盘是我的
This field is mine.
围栏也是我的
That fence is mine.
你把两个都破坏了
You damaged both.
然后又回来继续破坏
Then you came back to damage it more.
这是我的家
This is my home.
如果我把你家弄成这样  你会怎么办
If I did this to your home, what would you do?
我会杀了你
I'd kill you.
没错
That's right.
我的人说如果你们不走  我们就把你们埋在这里
My man said you if you didn't leave we'd bury you here.
但你们没有走
And you didn't leave.
这个山谷的人都很讲信用
We keep our word in this valley.
好吧  我们走
Fine. We'll leave.
不  不  太迟了
No, no, it's too late for that.
我说了我们这就走
I said we'll leave.
我不想让你们走了
I don't want you to leave.
给我挖
I want you to dig.
太阳要升起来了  先生
Sun's starting to heat up the sky, sir.
是啊
Yeah.
好了  够了
All right. That's enough.
没让你们出来
Nobody said get out.
不用多此一举了
Yeah, not much point in that.
我还有孩子
I have children.
我也有
So do I.
我觉得你的孩子没有你这个爸爸会更好
And from what I've seen, yours will be better off without you.
你是哪里人
Where are you from?
加州
California.
猜到了
Figures...
我把这些坑留着
I'm gonna leave these holes just like this.
就在我的地盘中央
Right here in the middle of my field.
如果你们再回来
And if you ever come back again,
我就把你们埋了  明白吗
I'm gonna fill em. You understand?
谢谢
Thank you.
我要的答案不是"谢谢"
"Thank you"'s not an answer.
照我说的做
You do what I say.
我要回加州
I'm going back to California.
蒙大拿不需要你
Montana doesn't want you.
蒙大拿不需要我
Montana doesn't want me.
我再也不会回来了  我发誓
I'm never coming back. I swear.
希望你能信守诺言
I'm gonna hold you to that.
我们应该不会再见到他们了
Don't think we'll be seeing them again.
嗯
Nope.
要我们把这些坑填上吗
Want us to fill these holes?
他们想在这里建个机场
They want to put an airport here.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
你打算怎么办
What do you want to do about it?
我还没想好
I'm not sure yet.
别填坑
Don't fill the holes.
-不填吗  -嗯
- No? - No.
-里普  -先生
- Rip? - Sir.
把我在营地的帐篷拆了
Have the boys take down my tent at camp.
我要搬回来住
I'm moving back to the lodge.
你确定吗
You sure you want me to do that?
你说不定还想上去看看呢
You might want to go up there some.
我确定
I'm sure.
我的夏天结束了
My summer's over.